FAILED should decline all open PT Applications
PENDING should navigate to the vo overview
PENDING should filter projects
PENDING should terminate vo projects
PENDING should relog with fm
PENDING should terminate fm projects
FAILED should generate a new ssh-keypair
PENDING should set a new ssh-keypair without previous generation
PENDING should navigate to the simple vm form
PENDING should fill the simple vm form
PENDING should submit the simple vm form
PENDING should successfully submitted the application
PENDING should load project overview
PENDING should have Bioinformatics in the research topics
PENDING should have dissemination
FAILED should navigate to application overview
PENDING should approve A SIMPLE VM APPLICATION
FAILED should navigate to project overview
PENDING should add member
PENDING should remove member
FAILED should navigate to application overview
PENDING should open the modification request modal
PENDING should have old values prefilled
PENDING should fill modification formular
PENDING should send a modification request
FAILED should navigate to application overview
PENDING should approve a simple vm modification request
PENDING should open the extension request modal
PENDING should fill extension formular
PENDING should send an extension request
FAILED should navigate to application overview
PENDING should approve a simple vm modification request
PENDING should navigate to the simple vm form
PENDING should fill the simple vm form
PENDING should submit the simple vm form
PENDING should successfully submitted the application
PENDING should load project overview
PENDING should have no pi set
PENDING pi should successfully approve application
PENDING should remove the application
FAILED should navigate to cloud application form
PENDING should fill cloud application form
PENDING should submit cloud application
PENDING should successfully submitted the application
PENDING should load project overview
PENDING should have Bioinformatics in the research topics
PENDING should have dissemination
FAILED should navigate to application overview
PENDING should approve cloud application with denbi default facility
PENDING should relog with facility manager
PENDING should navigate to facility overview
PENDING should approve cloud application
FAILED should navigate to openstack project overview
PENDING should open the modification request modal
PENDING should have old values prefilled
PENDING should fill modification formular
PENDING should send a modification request
PENDING should navigate to application overview
PENDING should approve a cloud  modification request
PENDING should relog with facility manager
PENDING should navigate to facility overview
PENDING should approve cloud application
FAILED should start a basic vm
PENDING should start a basic vm with a volume
PENDING should show all virtual machines as active
PENDING should shutdown the basic vm
PENDING should resume the basic vm
PENDING should delete the volume vm without deleting the volume
PENDING should delete the vm created volume
PENDING should create a snapshot of the basic vm
PENDING should start a vm with the  snapshot
PENDING should create and attach a volume to basic vm
PENDING should delete the snapshot of the basic vm
PENDING should should delete the basic vm without deleting the volume
PENDING should delete the manually created volume
PENDING should start a new vm
PENDING should show vm detail page with base functions for virtual machines working
PENDING should decline all open PT Applications
PENDING should navigate to the vo overview
PENDING should filter projects
PENDING should terminate vo projects
PENDING should relog with fm
PENDING should terminate fm projects